http://www.craworld.com/en/privacy-policy.aspx

Close
Close Browser Alert
Browser Compatibility Notification
It appears you are trying to access this site using an outdated browser.
As a result, parts of the site may not function properly for you.
We recommend updating your browser to its most recent version at your earliest convenience.
PerspectivesCase StudiesToggle SectionCase Studies SearchExpertiseToggle SectionAdvisoryToggle SectionAsset ManagementAsset Management SystemsAsset Performance and OptimisationAsset OperationsAssurance, Audit and ComplianceBusiness Case DevelopmentFinance and Economic AnalysisLogistics and Infrastructure PolicyRegulation and AccessRisk ManagementTransaction AdvisoryArchitecture and DesignBuildingsToggle SectionAsset Management SystemsDemolition and Decommissioning Digital DesignGeotechnicalInstrumentation and ControlLand Development and Urban PlanningToggle SectionLand DevelopmentUrban PlanningMaterials, Process and Plant EngineeringToggle SectionMaterials HandlingMinerals ProcessingPlant EngineeringMechanical, Electrical, Fire and Life SafetyToggle SectionElectrical Engineering - BuildingFire and Life Safety HVACHydraulics - BuildingProject ManagementToggle SectionProject and Construction ManagementStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilitySecurity, Information, Communication & TechnologyToggle SectionCommunication SystemsSecuritySpatial SciencesStructuresDigitalToggle SectionDigital IntelligenceD-LabOperational Resilience Supply Chain Resilience Workforce ResilienceConnected SitesCritical Infrastructure CybersecurityDigital Engineering ConsultingDigital TwinInnovation ExperienceOperational ResilienceSmart Cities and PlacesSupply Chain ResilienceWorkforce ResilienceEnergy and ResourcesToggle SectionAsset and Facilities ManagementChemicalsDamsEmergency ResponseGeologyGeotechnicalHSE Systems and Industrial HygieneImpact Assessment and PermittingInstrumentation and ControlIntegrated Water ManagementMaterials, Process and Plant EngineeringToggle SectionMaterials HandlingMinerals ProcessingPlant EngineeringMaterials TechnologyMechanical, Electrical, Fire and Life SafetyToggle SectionElectrical Engineering - BuildingFire and Life Safety HVACHydraulics - BuildingMining Engineering and GeosciencesOil and GasPowerProject and Construction ManagementRisk ManagementSpatial SciencesStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilityTailings (Mines and Residue)Wastewater Treatment and RecyclingTunnelsEPCMEnvironmentalToggle SectionAir and NoiseToggle SectionComputational Fluid DynamicsAquatic SciencesContamination Assessment and RemediationToggle SectionGuiding industry on PFAS managementDemolition and Decommissioning Environmental Strategy Consultation Food and AgricultureToggle SectionAgriculture Food ProcessingForestry ManagementHSE Systems and Industrial HygieneHydrogeologyHydrology and HydrodynamicsToggle SectionClimate ChangeWaterways and CoastalImpact Assessment and PermittingInternational Development Assistance (IDA)Maritime and Coastal EngineeringNatural ResourcesSpatial SciencesStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilitySustainability and Human RightsWaste ManagementFuture energyGeosciencesToggle SectionContamination Assessment and RemediationDamsGeologyGeotechnicalToggle SectionGeotechnical laboratory testingHydrogeologyMining GeosciencesRisk ManagementSpatial SciencesTailings (Mines and Residue)TunnelsProject ManagementToggle SectionConstruction ContractingEPCMInternational Development Assistance (IDA)Project and Construction ManagementStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilityTransportationToggle SectionAir and NoiseArchitecture, Interior Design, Landscape Architecture and Urban DesignAsset and Facilities ManagementAviationBridgesDigital DesignGeotechnicalImpact Assessment and PermittingMaritime and Coastal EngineeringMaterials TechnologyRailwaysRoad SystemsToggle SectionPavement EngineeringRoad Network ManagementRoad SystemsStructuresTransportation Planning and Traffic EngineeringStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilityTunnelsIntelligent Transport SystemsSustainability and Human RightsWaterToggle SectionAquatic SciencesDamsFood and AgricultureToggle SectionAgriculture Food ProcessingForestry ManagementHydrogeologyAutomationHydrology and HydrodynamicsToggle SectionClimate ChangeWaterways and CoastalImpact Assessment and PermittingIntegrated Water ManagementInternational Development Assistance (IDA)Maritime and Coastal EngineeringSpatial SciencesStakeholder Engagement and Social SustainabilityWastewater and Stormwater Collection SystemsWastewater Treatment and RecyclingWater Treatment and DesalinationToggle SectionDesalinationWater TreatmentWater Transmission and Distribution Construction ContractingCareersToggle SectionOpportunitiesToggle SectionGraduates and studentsLife@GHDWork@GHDContactToggle SectionFeedback FormAbout UsToggle SectionAnnual ReviewCommunityInclusion and DiversityToggle SectionA journey of ‘firsts’ – Jasmine’s inspiring careerMartin’s surrogacy adventure to destination dadHealth, Safety and EnvironmentHistoryToggle SectionA Firm FoundationBreaking New GroundIntegrity ManagementNews and InsightsToggle SectionInsightsToggle SectionWaterToggle SectionHow to activate infrastructure stimulus through accelerated assessmentPreventing catastrophic water main failureEnergy & ResourcesToggle SectionGHD Advisory Delivers Landmark Rehabilitation Plan for Port Terminal EnvironmentToggle SectionA Flexible Approach to Using eDNACommunity resilience and coronavirusDeveloping effective fishways: Advances in fish passage modellingProperty & BuildingsToggle SectionHow agile, data-driven strategies will drive high street recoveryTransportationDigitalToggle SectionFostering resilient workplace productivityMaintaining construction site productivity creates new normal for safety
Moving from Smart Cities to smart outcomes that can better prepare for future crisisThe difficulties of “yes”Uplifting Accessible Communications and Services for the Digital CitizenVirtual collaboration for speedy infrastructure deliverySmart Cities and Places – live free or die hardAdvisoryProject ManagementPlanning for uncertaintyNon-revenue water lossesAchieving business sustainabilityFlood Modelling and Water meter CalibrationWaste to Energy for Wastewater TreatmentIntegrated Water ManagementResource Recovery from WastewaterTransitioning to customer-centric apporachesGroundwater Quality Monitoring at CCR UnitsCalifornia children affected by lead poisoningWater Recycling Fund ProgramUpgrading Kangaroo Creek DamComplying with industrial stormwater planning updatesEPA 2017 Stormwater Construction General PermitFiltering microplasticsLead in Drinking WaterPermitting for industrial stormwater discharge in IllinoisStorm Water Grant Program (SWGP)Water Recycling Fund ProgramMicrogrid in WAEPA 2017 Stormwater Construction General PermitPermitting for industrial stormwater discharge in IllinoisCourt upholds emission monitoring for oil and gasStorm Water Grant Program (SWGP)Enabling electricity evolutionGroundwater Quality Monitoring at CCR UnitsInfrastructure owners face changeProposed emission reductions for oil and gasUnderground storage closure requirementsUS Congress votes to lift US oil export banEPA 2017 Stormwater Construction General PermitManaging OutrageGroundwater Quality Monitoring at CCR UnitsLead in Drinking WaterProposed emission reductions for oil and gasUSEPA intends to expand the Risk Management ProgramTransforming perspectives on complex sitesComplying with chemical data reportingRisk Assessment and Toxicology Update On TSCA ReformCourt upholds emission monitoring for oil and gasBenzene Fenceline Monitoring ProgramCalifornia Organics Diversion Regulatory UpdateCalifornia children affected by lead poisoningChange Notification to ISO 14001:2015Task force recommendations for expedited site cleanupProposed Revisions to Site Remediation MACTNew Ontario online registry for environmental permitsFederal guidance released for human health risk assessmentsRevised UST regulationsLead levels updated for remediationRemediation guidance for adaptive site managementUSEPA intends to expand the Risk Management ProgramNew toxicity values for EPA screening calculatorTSCA Reform is on its way to become a lawNew Strategy for Waste-Free OntarioFinal ruling issued on exposure to Crystalline SilicaFill and Excess Soil Regulatory UpdateEPA 2017 Stormwater Construction General PermitFuture of Western SydneyUSEPA Vapor Intrusion Technical GuideHazard awareness training for demolition servicesBig DataDigital TechnologiesDigital DisruptionCanada hosts international forum on public private partnershipsPublic private partnership forum examines lessons for transitNew Strategy for Waste-Free OntarioHazard awareness training for demolition servicesComplying with chemical data reportingFill and Excess Soil Regulatory UpdateProject Management for Large Transport ProjectsPublic private partnership forum examines lessons for transitCanada hosts international forum on public private partnershipsTransforming perspectives on complex sitesRisk Assessment and Toxicology Update On TSCA ReformCritical insights from P3 2017 in Toronto, CanadaPioneering New Energy SystemsToggle SectionProtecting Critical Energy InfrastructureFast track new energy grid connectionPumped for pumped hydro projects?Maintaining power system strength Solving the PFAS puzzleHow major rail is keeping pace Unlocking new markets through transport logistics modellingUpgrade your approach to accessing real-time data with Live Asset Management PlansEnvironmental data and public communications for fast-tracked infrastructure projectsOn your marks, shovel ready, go…!Mapping an underwater world in 3DThe information age and creating a growth mindset in the workforceWhat's your asset data worth?Environmental, Social and Governance Factors Driving Infrastructure UpgradesDiscovering Digital Disruptors to Drive Change Digital Engineering – a transformational opportunity for the industryDigital risk – adding business value in a transformative ageEaster Egg emergenciesFaster Smart CitiesHow Businesses Can Weather the StormPriority project types identified for proposed Canadian Federal Offset ProgramResilience and risk in mining water managementMaking strides in PFAS treatment technology with alkaline ozonation study Rethinking coastal hazard managementFive tips to safely re-open and increase capacity at sporting venuesnewsheaderNewsToggle SectionAdani Carmichael Coal Mine ProjectChanging the world in TorontoDavid Kinniburgh named Regional General Manager - UAEDesigning a net-zero energy plan with the Australian Academy of ScienceGHD Advisory supports BP Australia’s sustainable hydrogen feasibility studyGHD appointed to design new Navy facilities in Western Australia
GHD joins Australian Hydrogen CouncilGHD Provides Social Distancing Solution to NHS Children’s Hospital GHD to implement Digital Train Control for Cross River Rail GHD is leading the way in Waste Management across AustraliaGHD is taking the lead in the competition for future talentGrowing our natural resources expertise with addition of Niblett Environmental Associates teamLandmark UAE park named Education Project of the YearPreparing Australian electricity systems for large-scale hydrogen productionPoll shows employees are uncomfortable returning to work without social distancing measures Reinventing engineering for a rapidly changing worldQatar field hospital designed from scratch in less than two weeksOur industrial hygiene team keeps employees safe as they return to workTransforming transport in regional South AustraliaA balancing act: Getting to grips with biodiversity offsetting and mitigation bankingA message from Water for Women on International Women’s DayAquaLAB Connect helps shape the digital future of waterAuckland’s Lightpath cycleway takes the lead with prestigious awardAuckland’s Lightpath shines at NZ planning awardsAdvising on one of Australia’s largest infrastructure transactionsCelebrating Australia’s top projectsArizona water reclamation facility helps conserve groundwaterBeaton Client Choice AwardsStrength in North America highlights our ability to serve clients and communities in uncertain timesGHD Advisory named Australasia’s #1 technical advisor for transactionsGHD’s new NZ leader focuses on high performanceDemonstrating our market leadership in CanadaGHD appoints Sheila Mistry as People Leader for UKGHD Advisory strengthens UAE teamDeveloping a first-of-its-kind mangrove park for UAEGlobal merger delivers integrated data-led consultingNew operations lead will help drive growth in the northeast United StatesGHD helps Middle East clients address energy challenges GHD’s Global Digital Leader moves to North AmericaGHD helps students to embrace Indo-Pacific opportunities
Collaboration to provide innovative new wireless stormwater monitoring solutionGHD welcomes National Strategy to support a thriving hydrogen industryNew beginnings: How Nivine re-started her career in AustraliaGHD Digital’s Jacyl Shaw named ‘Microsoft Executive Leader of the Year’GHD reinforces strategic focus in North AmericaNew operations lead will help drive growth in the northeast United StatesGHD partners with Galliford Try on Yorkshire Water Civils FrameworkGHD celebrates 10 years in Papua New GuineaCreating a single source of truth for digital dataTop honors for water engineerWelcome Jim Giannopoulos as our new Executive General Manager, CanadaEngineering a new future for Melbourne’s iconic 1920s Capitol TheatreGHD at the centre of Australia's hydrogen industry developmentGHD at WEFTEC 2019Rising to meet the challenges of an evolving environmental marketGHD rises higher in global design rankingsGHD transforms Queensland’s Daydream Island resortSaskya Hunter named as one of Australia’s Most Innovative Engineers 2019How hybrid energy will unlock the potential of Northern AustraliaMore than 100 GHD global technical leaders connect with government and business leaders in CairnsGHD helps young professionals navigate their careers in the digital ageGHD and Australia’s gas import industry set milestoneGHD Advisory appoints leader for UAEGHD provides remediation services to Clydebridge Chemicals Showcasing Pacific development projects and partnerships GHD and FCG combine to enhance client services in Northern Australia GHD helps Sydney Metro Northwest project arrive on timeGHD internship cements passion for development workGHD wins NCE100 Impact in Energy awardGHD ranks among top design companies in North America Industry leader, Kurt Beil, joins GHD as Market Leader, Environment GHD a winner in the 2019 RoSPA AwardsGHD Young Professional recognised by Institution of Chemical EngineersGHD appoints new Operations Manager, QatarGHD Digital launches AquaLAB to transform how the water industry operates in the digital ageDemonstrating the value of inclusion and making it happenThe future of the UK water sector - interview with Stewart TennantFrom Iraq to Australia – Marvin’s career journeyGHD acheives prestigious safety certification in OntarioGHD announces the appointment of new Regional Principal to lead the northeast United StatesNew GHD Advisory leader sets pathway for future growthGHD doubles down on growthGHD technical award recognizes groundbreaking projectHarnessing hydropower potential in the PhilippinesGrantley Hall – Blending the old with the newGHD strengthens its rail capabilityGHD helps to improve connectivity and boost sustainable travel GHD honored by the Greater Kitchener Waterloo Chamber of Commerce for employee engagementInfrastructure event connects with European clientsGHD recruits transmission expert to inspire innovation in energy sectorGHD app design wins at inaugural NSW Roads and Maritime Services Innovation Network InitiativeToggle SectionGHD Digital’s expansion into North America focuses on Digital Disruption and the Fourth Industrial RevolutionGHD Digital’s expansion into North America focuses on Digital Disruption and the Fourth Industrial RevolutionGHD wins Asia Pacific award for pesticide container management project in the PacificGHD expands its air and noise modelling capabilityLooking back on the 2018 GHD ChallengeGHD appoints Simon Light as new General Manager for Europe and Middle EastLooking back on the 2018 GHD ChallengeGHD appoints Simon Light as new General Manager for Europe and Middle EastSpecial moments for GHD’s Spatial teamGHD wins place on YORConsult2 frameworkGHD sponsors global interns as part of Australia’s New Colombo PlanGHD recognized as one of Waterloo Area’s Top Employers for 2019GHD receives industry accreditation for its commitment to developing young engineersAdvising on one of Australia’s largest infrastructure transactionsGHD announces new Transportation Market Leader for AustraliaGHD appoints new Indigenous Services Leader
Our year in reviewHow to thrive on your career journeyGHD celebrates opening of Lake Jackson, Texas officeWhat happens when majestic wind turbines come to townGHD sets benchmark for environmental assessments in the PhilippinesGHD recognised as a carer-friendly employerGHD engineers new neuroscience department at Monash UniversityGHD extends its global tunnelling experienceWednesday is “Poppy Day”GHD helps improve management of pesticide containers in the PacificGHD Digital and Orange Business Services deliver instant intelligent insights to Australasian enterprisesGHD helps return Blacktown Native Institution to Indigenous custodiansToggle SectionReducing Air Pollution - Guiding clients through the complexities of the Medium Combustion Plant Directive GHD grows UAE team to help take client projects from masterplanning to reality GHD to deliver Australian Sports Partnership Program to build healthy, inclusive communities through sport.GHD and Olsson Fire & Risk join forces in New Zealand and AustraliaGHD wins Bronze at International Water Association Project Innovation AwardsGHD appoints new Market Leader – Water in AustraliaGHD achieves Silver Corporate Partnership status with Institution of Chemical EngineersGHD partners with Jacobs for longest section of Australia’s Inland Rail programOmni-Means officially adopts GHD name and brand following merger completionGHD expands Intelligent Transport Systems capabilities Part-time geologist, full-time dadGHD Digital and Mindtree create platform-based services to cater for digital transformationGHD wins Engineers Australia award for Brisbane Airport runway resurfacingGHD grows in the global environmental marketMassive roof replacement project recognised for engineering excellenceGHD is responding to the ‘fourth industrial revolution’ and client demand Championing diversity in the workplaceGlobal leader helps GHD transform client serviceGlobal survey charts GHD’s growth trajectory GHD appoints new Technical Director in UKFive ways to celebrate Indigenous peoples and cultureWater for Women announces the first round of research award recipientsTasmanian renewable energy leaders share vision for collaborative futureGHD’s suite of services helps a new mine to proceedGHD Advisory’s Infrastructure Investment and Economics (IIE) services go globalGHD and Water for Women Fund celebrate World Environment DayGHD provides continuity of service to Wannon WaterWater for Women Fund celebrates Menstrual Hygiene Day GHD is bringing Paris to DohaGHD wins NCE100 Excellence in Water awardNew approach to defend infrastructure from cyberattacksGHD boosts operational performance in UK transport sectorProud to be LGBTI, proud to be GHDTen tips for returning to work after parental leavePrestigious appointment for GHD’s chief counsel in the United States GHD announces new Operations Director in Manchester, UKGHD a winner in the 2018 RoSPA AwardsGHD helps improve transport infrastructure in Papua New GuineaTrailblazer to lead GHD’s Canberra and Southern NSW businessGHD in New Zealand diversifies its business with the launch of GHD Digital.Five technologies that will drive your freight forward fasterGHD expands in the UAE with new Dubai officeGHD stars shine at Engineering Excellence AwardsLNAPL clean-up guidance releasedGHD recognised as top engineering companyFour inspiring pieces of advice from Jamila RizviGroundwater discharges may become subject to the Clean Water ActEngineering innovation secures civil engineering excellence awardGHD and the Regional Municipality of York receive OPWA award for technical innovationPFAS New fact sheets provide guidance on emerging contaminantsWhen a talented photographer becomes a bridge inspectorWorld Health DayConfirming our commitment to Waterloo Region Global insight for Australia’s electricity networks:GHD in New Zealand boosts its business to support growthGHD grows security offering in SydneyGHD recognised for supporting Defence reservists Global industry leader in power substation design joins GHDGHD to deliver concept design for raising Warragamba Dam in SydneyGHD Advisory expands to North America to support asset ownersTop five ingredients for Badgerys Creek Aerotropolis to riseA message from Water for Women on International Women’s DaySix ways to position yourself for successWhat SaaS tells you about MaaSNew Colombo intern discovers a new side to engineering at GHDGHD expands to Guildford, UKClient service helps realise world-leading energy projectsShaping the Western Sydney AerotropolisYoung design pioneer recognised at BIM AwardsClient award highlights GHD’s safety focusGHD announces new Manager for SydneyGHD is recognised as employer of choice for gender equality for fourth year in a rowGHD strengthens digital leadershipGHD appoints new Legal Counsel, Europe and Middle EastSmart Seeds grows fresh ideas for future infrastructureGHD enhances services for Chinese investorsGHD partners with Sydney Water for drought reliefGHD says “Bula” to New Colombo intern in FijiPushing the boundaries of BIMGHD is part of the growth trend in the trenchless marketGHD boosts capabilities to support social sustainabilityGHD strengthens hydropower capabilityWater for Women Fund Commences - Request for Proposals for WASH Research AwardsGHD helps deliver Water for Women FundToggle SectionTech Sprint generates game changing solution to construction productivity problemGHD strengthens Board diversityGHD outlines the future of project managementGHD contributes to UK’s Northern Energy Task ForceContinuing to invest in future leadershipI-TAP NQ turns to fresh ideas for North Queensland’s infrastructure challengesForce main replacement work wins ACEC award in ArizonaGHD announces Market Development Director for Europe and Middle EastGHD announces record performanceInsights from the Infrastructure Investors Forum AustraliaToggle SectionGHD’s laptop donation supports women’s health services in Wagga WaggaGHD expands to TaurangaInfrastructure and logistics expert joins GHD AdvisoryEcological restoration earns landscape architecture awardGHD recognised as a leader in the global environmental marketToggle SectionGHD tops technical advisor league tableGHD recognised globally as a design leaderNew facility preserves Australian history for the futureGHD expands contaminated land capabilities in QueenslandToggle SectionEnergy storage project opens new horizons for remote microgridGHD highlights smart solutions for the mining sectorGHD storms to the top at RICS Yorkshire and Humber AwardsGlobal role highlights how sport changes livesGHD expands contaminated land capabilities in QueenslandEnergy storage project opens new horizons for remote microgridGHD highlights smart solutions for the mining sectorGHD storms to the top at RICS Yorkshire and Humber AwardsGlobal role highlights how sport changes livesGHD leadership appointments capitalise on New Zealand infrastructure trendsToggle SectionGHD helps revitalise open channel with new parklandWastewater rehabilitation work wins project of the year in ArizonaGHD announces new Chairman and executive directorsGHD ranks among top designers in North AmericaGHD announces new UK leaderGHDWoodhead and Creative Spaces launch new brand in New ZealandGHD enhances energy security in the KimberleyGHD continues streak of outstanding waste management achievementsFrom dump to park: GHD helps turn environmental issue into Saipan’s new landmarkGHD expands asset management team in AucklandGHD improves road safety on Pokeno to Mangatarata corridor in New ZealandDigital transformation and growth expert joins GHD AdvisoryBeaton Client Choice AwardsGHD earns recognition for innovative projects in York Region, OntarioGHD and Omni-Means merge to expand transportation servicesGHD helps realise landmark footbridge in time for Australian OpenToggle SectionGHD Challenge brings together construction industry to support charitiesGHD announces its largest office in North AmericaGHD celebrates 50 years of contributions to Canberra and beyondPush to change flexibility culture for both men and women earns GHD gender equality recognitionGHD demonstrates inspirational consulting leadershipGHD celebrates outstanding public works achievementsGHD Advisory supports asset owners in a transforming worldGHD wins global award for Guam landfill closureEngaging stakeholders for irrigation success in Australia’s food bowlToggle SectionGHD celebrates outstanding achievements in South AustraliaGHD channels multidisciplinary skills for landmark irrigation upgradeGHD switches on the tap for new water technologiesGHD recognized globally for Guam landfill closureGHD delivers transformational engineering projects for WAToggle SectionGHD’s Power team boosts capacity in NewcastleGHD helps realise outstanding project management achievementsGHD shines at New Zealand consulting engineering awardsGHD unites UK operations under single brandGHD engineers named Australia’s innovation leadersGHD continues global growth trajectoryGHD adds momentum to Sydney transport teamGHD and SMEC joint venture appointed as Independent Verifier for Gold Coast Light Rail Stage 2GHD sustains performance in global environmental marketGHD helps realise a new health research hub for UAEAuckland’s Lightpath cycleway takes the lead with prestigious awardGHD announces new leaders in AustraliaDisrupting Auckland – new urban ideas take centre stage at Smart Seeds ShowcaseGHD hits refresh on governance structureGHD’s rail business gathers momentum with new appointmentGHD recognises client service at its bestToggle SectionAuckland’s Lightpath shines at NZ planning awardsCreating a new gateway to Western AustraliaGHD recognized among top design companies in USA and CanadaLeadership transition builds on GHD’s model of successToggle SectionGHD leaders pledge for parity for International Women’s DayHigh five for GHD’s waste management teamGHD supports Arriva’s success as it retains London Overground concessionGHD names new Europe and Middle East leaderGHD’s water leader acknowledged for global contributionsGHD supports Arriva's success as it begins the Northern Powerhouse transformationGHD Woodhead steps up in global rankingsGHD’s Defence business grows in AustraliaExtended water partnership builds on a record of successGHD acknowledged by Consult Australia for industry leadershipGHD strengthens focus on Defence project deliveryGHD recognised for digital leadershipWorking together to help mitigate climate change in OntarioGHD strides forward with gender equalityGHD engineer achieves unique certification in GuamToowoomba infrastructure project wins bigGHD people help reimagine Western SydneyGHD helps realise artistic visions in ChristchurchGHD's young professionals support kids in careGHD appoints transportation leader in North QueenslandCRA Europe adopts GHD nameGHD celebrates 10 years in NowraEngineers Australia commends GHD’s gender diversity focusGHD steps up in global rankingsGHD boosts New Zealand business with high-profile appointmentsGHD appoints Defence LeaderGHD’s CEO among engineering leadersGHD and CRA complete integrationGHD improves human and environmental wellbeingGHD and GHA Livigunn grow together in the UKGHD helps deliver first shared street in South AustraliaSydney ideas bloom at Smart SeedsGHD ranks highly in North AmericaVideo showcases bridge replacement workGHD presents water innovations in AdelaideGHD enhances services for health and aged care clientsGraduates join consulting ranks at GHDGHD celebrates 10 years in ToowoombaGHD helps achieve tunnelling milestones at Grosvenor MineGHD helps realize award-winning Levi’s Stadium in CaliforniaInfrastructure innovation blooms with Smart SeedsCRA celebrates 10 years as one of Canada’s Best Managed CompaniesGHD leads the waste sector four years in a rowEnvironmental accolade for GHD-CRA mergerStrategic appointment expands GHD’s Federal businessToggle SectionGHD ranks highly for defence servicesGHD enhances market presence in property and buildings sectorGHD supports Indigenous professionals of the futureGHD signs contract to transform Perth’s most congested roadsGHD appoints Dr Paul Nathanail as Technical Director – Contaminated LandGHD's UK Water division partners with firm to support Thames Water's capital programmes frameworkShaping a global response to Covid-19GHD supports Santos study to decarbonise natural gas into “blue hydrogen” Bringing the power of hydrogen to homes is a step closerDesign work has commenced on $400M Western Australia road and rail project2020 Most Innovative Engineers - AustraliaMovement Strategies commissioned by the SGSABudding humanitarian engineers win internships at GHD How Sarah Gilmour is making her mark in geosciencesDelivering next-generation and future-proof education centres across regional NSWGHD and University of Melbourne to dive deeper into underwater noiseGHD appointed by Galliford Try for Monk Bridge development scheme in Leeds, UKMovement Strategies commissioned by the SGSA and EFL to assess the application of social distancingMajor renewable power projects ‘switched on’ for summer in Western AustraliaWastewater testing service to provide early COVID-19 detection and outbreak reductionDelivering Australia’s largest airport solar energy installation GHD appoints Jonathan Edwards as Transport Market Leader for EMEAGHD expands Advisory-led operations into Singapore to strengthen Asia-Pacific presenceGHD and E7 are improving project performance visibility for clientsTasmania’s first Roads Australia FellowGHD award celebrates innovative approaches for PFAS cleanupSolutions to help in the fight against COVID-19 at long-term care facilitiesWater Awards recognise innovative Filtration Plant upgradeA green revolution for our communitiesDesigning the world’s largest steel undercover ship modularisation and sustainment facilityAward-winning undersea cable improves connections between Australia, Asia and USAGreen Book 2020 – a good step forward, but more is neededFuture-proofing Defence estate in New ZealandPublicationsInsightsToggle SectionCommitted to communitiesToggle SectionAdvancing remote asset inspections with new technologiesCommunity resilience and coronavirusConnectCOVID-19: How to flatten the curve with dataEight tips to maintain human connection in virtual environmentsGHD designs 504-bed field hospital in Qatar from scratch in less than two weeksGHD's response to COVID-19How can I maintain compliance during USEPA's Temporary Enforcement Discretion Policy?How can we use data insights to modify our environmental impact in a post coronavirus world?Remote tools to optimize collaborative problem solving in a virtual environmentStanding stronger togetherTen emerging trends shaping our new futureThe difficulties of “yes”The new normalTime to scale-up cyber awareness to keep the lights on and water flowing Why pandemic times need a startup mindsetProtecting your assets in uncertain timesGHD Provides Social Distancing Solution to NHS Children’s Hospital Advancing virtual learning through Building Information Modelling The opportunities of ‘yes’Stimulus funds and shovel ready transportation projectsElevating new forms of data integrity for future asset adaptabilityNew urban realities and building back for good
Learning from COVID-19 to build a stronger, more resilient organizationOur leadership Toggle SectionOur BoardExecutive Management GroupGovernanceProud to be employee ownedSustainabilityValues and Culture
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
This Privacy Policy outlines how GHD1 and its related entities and affiliates (collectively “GHD”) collects, uses and stores personal information in the course of its business from employees, applicants for employment, contractors, clients, suppliers and other individuals (referred to as “you” or “your” in this Privacy Policy).
GHD respects and upholds your right to privacy protection. GHD recognises applicable local laws and regulations and relevant data protection standards in respect of the collection, use, disclosure storage and transfer of personal information from individuals.
This Privacy Policy details the practices we have adopted to protect your privacy so that you can understand how we manage your “personal information”, any “personally identifiable information” or “personal data” (as defined under the European Union's General Data Protection Regulation or “GDPR”) (together collectively referred to as “personal information” in this Privacy Policy), you entrust to us.
This Privacy Policy also sets out how you can contact us in relation to your personal information and, if requested by you, opt-out of this Privacy Policy, limit the use of, or amend, any personal information we may have about you.
By providing us with personal information about yourself through our website, any GHD webpage or otherwise, you consent to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and transfer of that personal information as set out in this Policy. If at any time, you wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and transfer of your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, you may opt-out by contacting us (refer to the Contact Us information below) or by immediately ceasing to provide any further personal information about yourself to GHD via its website or otherwise.
COVID-19 ResponseIn the interest of protecting our employee’s health and discharging our duty of care to invitees to our premises, GHD may, during the COVID-19 Pandemic, collect and use additional sensitive personal information from our employees and visitors [to be specified if possible, e.g. such as whether they have flu-like symptoms, have been in contact with anyone infected with COVID-19, or travelled to a high-risk area]. Only the minimum necessary personal information reasonably necessary in order to prevent or manage COVID-19 in the workplace will be collected, used or disclosed. It will be managed in accordance with this policy and it will only be disclosed to the persons who need to have access to such personal information for the performance of their duties. The primary purpose for collection of that additional information is to ensure that necessary precautions are adopted in relation to that individual and any other individuals. Under most jurisdictions an exemption from any requirement for consent to collect and use is permitted in circumstances of serious threat to health or safety of an individual. GHD will comply with an specific COVID-19 guidance issued by a relevant regulator.
Overview of this Policy
1. When do we collect and store personal information?
Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you (either directly or indirectly), and may be collected directly from you, by a third party you have given consent to disclosing your personal information, or by a credit agency, government or statutory body.
We collect and store personal information (including names, telephone numbers, address, email address, occupation, education and qualifications, etc) in a range of contexts, such as:
when entering into relationships with new clients or potential clients
when individuals apply for employment or other business opportunities with us
when individuals register online for access to secure sites or collaboration services hosted by GHD or third parties on behalf of GHD including, GHD Clientnet™, ProjectWise, BIM360, ArcGIS Online, or other services, and
when we conduct surveys, community consultation, environmental and other studies as part of our business
2. What do we do with personal information?
We may use your personal information:
to enable us to provide services to you or our clients
to communicate information about our services
for our internal administrative, planning, product development, marketing and research requirements, or
to consider the suitability of applicants for employment with us, which may be processed by third parties engaged to undertake pre-employment screening services, or for any other reason you allow or consent us to
As an example, one of the key objectives of GHD’s website is to provide information about who we are, what we do and our local and global professional capabilities. We may collect personal information to update our website and in order to provide relevant information about GHD, our services, our key people in our regions or our capabilities in a variety of contexts.
3. Reasons we may share or disclose your personal information
Whilst at all times complying with this Privacy Policy and having primary regard for the protection of your personal information, GHD may share or disclose your personal information in a number of circumstances, such as:
to GHD group entities
to other GHD offices
in the course of your employment
when passing information between GHD offices, credit, law enforcement, and government agencies, and professional services providers, if required, or
with your consent or as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any service you have requested of us or authorised
Some examples:
As part of the provision of our services, we may outsource some of our functions to third parties, which may involve the disclosure of your personal information. These third parties will not be authorised to use your personal information for any purpose or purposes other than that for which your personal information is disclosed.
GHD is a global organisation. We may disclose your personal information to GHD offices in countries outside the country in which it was collected, if it is necessary for one of the purposes the information has been disclosed to us. For example, if you send us an application for employment in one country we may send it to one of our offices in another country to consider whether that office may be in a position to offer you employment.
GHD technology support is provided from the Philippines and, for that purpose, your personal information may be accessed remotely from the Philippines.
GHD employee personal information and employment/personnel records are stored securely and used in the jurisdiction in which it is collected and relevant to the particular GHD employee.
If we disclose your personal information to an office in a country other than the country in which it is collected, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure a level of data protection at least as protective of that required in the European Union's GDPR, which offers high levels of personal information protection.
We will also require any GHD employees, subcontractors or agents who are outside your jurisdiction and to whom we transfer information about you to ensure a similar level of data protection as required by the European Union's GDPR when it comes to protecting your personal information. GHD will not use, share or disclose your personal information that was collected for a particular purpose for another secondary purpose (which you would not reasonably expect) without your consent unless we are required or authorised by law, or compelled for legitimate legal reasons by government authority or law enforcement agency. GHD must seek additional consent from you to use or retain your personal information other than as set out in this Privacy Policy and you have the choice to opt-out at all times by contacting us (as outlined below).
Your personal information is never shared, sold, rented or otherwise disclosed except if required by law or with your consent.
4. Marketing and communications
GHD is driven by a client-service led culture. For this reason, we may send marketing material or communicate information that we think may be relevant or of interest to you or your industry or provide you with details about our latest services that you may benefit from.At any time, you may opt-out of receiving any communications from us (other than as required for the operation of our business, for example, regarding payment of accounts) or change your marketing communication preferences.Electronic marketing or communications material will have an “unsubscribe” link or contain instructions allowing you to opt-out or change your preferences. Alternatively, you can contact us directly about our marketing and communications by using the contact details below.
4.01 California residents and direct marketingCalifornia residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding GHD’s disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. It should be noted that GHD does not disclose personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, regardless of jurisdiction.
5. How do we use "cookies", "log files", data analytics and other similar technology?
5.01 CookiesThe GHD website located at http://www.ghd.com and the GHD Clientnet™ both use cookies for collecting information.A “cookie” is a small data file that is placed on your computer or other device to allow a website to recognise you as a user when you return to the website using the same computer and web browser, either for the duration of your visit (using a ‘session cookie’) or for repeat visits (a ‘persistent cookie’). Other similar files work in the same way and we use the word “cookie” in this Privacy Policy to refer to all files that collect information in this way.
You may disable cookies by changing the settings on your browser – please refer to your browser options or instructional material. If you disable cookies, it is likely to affect how your browser works. For more information on cookies visit: www.allaboutcookies.org.
5.02 Log filesThe GHD Client Portal website located at http://www.ghdwa.com/ (a website which is operated by a third party) uses log files on a limited basis to record appropriate access to some project information by registered users.
A log file or log is the automatically produced and time-stamped documentation of events relevant to a particular system. From the server’s log files, an administrator can identify numbers of visitors, the domains from which they are visiting, the number of requests for each page and usage patterns.
5.03 Data analytics (such as Google Analytics™) and other technologies
The GHD website located at http://www.ghd.com uses log files and Google Analytics™.We may automatically log IP addresses (i.e., the electronic addresses of computers connected to the Internet) to analyse trends, administer the site, track user movements, and gather broad demographic information.
We may collect and use data relating to the geographical location of your computer or mobile internet device. We use this to provide country and region-specific information.
This information collected is not “personal information” and you cannot be identified from its collection. It is only used to assist GHD in optimising the content and effectiveness of our website.
5.04 HTML5 local storage
HTML5 local storage is used to store information locally and survives browser sessions. Its main purpose within the GHD website relates to automatically logging IP addresses to allow for region specific websites to load. Many Internet browsers allow you to disable HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in HTML5 local storage using browser controls.
6. Links to third party websites
Websites operated by us may contain links to other websites that are operated by third parties. Whilst GHD tries to link only websites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we make no representations or warranties as to the privacy practices of any third-party site and cannot be responsible for the privacy policies, content or security of other sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, or cover, linked websites.
If you access or share information to websites linked to our website, the operators of those websites may collect your information in accordance with their own privacy policies that may differ to ours. You should review the privacy, “cookie” and other policies displayed on these websites to find out how your personal information may be used and stored.
7. Data security
We will take all reasonable steps and apply appropriate technical and organisational measures to maintain the security of any personal information we receive from you and protect it from loss, misuse, and unauthorised access, disclosure or modification.
We use a variety of secure techniques to store and protect your information, including secure GHD IT systems and firewalls. Any digital transfer of personal information is secured using a range of security methods. GHD is constantly reviewing its information security technology and practices.
We will only keep your personal information when we consider it necessary for one of the purposes for which you have disclosed it. If it is no longer necessary to keep your personal information, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information safely, if required.
8. How can you access and correct information?
You may have a right in certain circumstances to request a copy of the personal information about you we may hold, request the removal of personal information from our records and to have inaccurate information changed or out-of-date information amended. For example, persons in the European Union, have a right under the GDPR to request the deletion or erasure of their personal information, where that information is no longer required for the purpose for which it was collected.
Please submit a request to the relevant GHD office, the Integrity Officer, or via the Contact Us link on our website, and we will respond to your request as required by applicable law.For security reasons, we will ask you to verify your identity to ensure that we do not give information to the wrong person or change or remove your personal information without your express consent.If there is no applicable legal or regulatory requirement for GHD to respond to your request, GHD will respond at its discretion.
9. Children’s information
GHD websites and collaboration services hosted by GHD or third parties on behalf of GHD are intended to be used by adults and corporate entities interested in GHD. They are not intended for children, and GHD does not knowingly collect or store personal information about children under the age of 13.
10. Data breach notification
In the highly unlikely event of a data breach, GHD will act promptly to comply with applicable local laws. Where it is reasonably foreseeable that an individual will suffer as a result of a data breach, the relevant regulatory body and, where possible, the affected individual will be contacted without undue delay. This notification shall include the nature of the breach, the personal data possibly involved and measures taken to address the breach (including to reduce the harm of negative consequences), the contact details for whom affected individuals can obtain further information and details of any assistance being provided to affected individuals.
11. Future changes to our Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and GHD is committed to our privacy practices being up-to-date with prevailing best practices and changes in local laws, regulations and data protection standards and technology.
Given this, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time and will notify you by posting an updated version of our Privacy Policy on our website. The amended policy will apply between us as and when it is posted on our website. This document represents GHD’s Privacy Policy as at 1 April 2020.
12. How to contact us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, wish to opt-out of our Privacy Policy or have any complaint regarding the treatment of your privacy or personal information by us, please contact a local GHD office, use the Contact Us link on our website, or contact our Integrity Officer using the details set out below. Any genuine concerns or complaints will be investigated and responded to in line with local law.
Integrity Officer
c/- Office of the Company Secretary
Level 15, 133 Castlereagh Street
Sydney NSW 2000
Email: integrity.officer@ghd.com
Website: www.ghd.com
If you are not satisfied with a response, dependent on your location, you may have an option to refer your complaint to a relevant privacy regulator. We will provide you details of any relevant regulator on request.
1"GHD” is a reference to GHD Group Pty Ltd and includes any company carrying on business that is part of the GHD group of companies.
Top
